<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quest For Glory</string>

    <string name="main_description">You are sitting in office, quite an ordinary day. Nothing was pointing out that this will be most important day for hero in his rising up to glory.\n\nSuddenly, out of nowhere, mail appears in your inbox.\nWhat will you do?</string>
    <string name="main_ichigo_kurosaki_ichigo">Ignore the mail. You are not a hero…\n(go to Ichigo, Kurosaki Ichigo)</string>
    <string name="main_hero_in_its_making">This is what I’ve been waiting for, I will open the CASE\n(go to Hero in its making)</string>

    <string name="ichigo_kurosaki_ichigo_label">Ichigo, Kurosaki Ichigo</string>
    <string name="ichigo_kurosaki_ichigo_description">You pierced sword through one ninja\'s chest, by corner of the eye, you noticed 4 more coming from behind. You thrown shurikens just to get some time, knowing that it can’t do any harm to this hard cored ninjas. But that was enough, you grabbed first ninja for arm and used him as shield against piercing attack from…\nAnd then you woke up… It was about time, another day finished… You can go</string>
    <string name="ichigo_kurosaki_ichigo_button_text">(go to Problem?)</string>

    <string name="hero_in_its_making_label">Hero in its making</string>
    <string name="hero_in_its_making_description">Suddenly… Le wild Dakinsa appears asking to open the CASE.</string>
    <string name="hero_in_its_making_le_wild_dakinsa">Le wild Dakinsa</string>
    <string name="hero_in_its_making_problem">Great! I have better things to do. Let him open it\n(go to Problem?)</string>
    <string name="hero_in_its_making_clark_gable">No! Sometimes man has to do what man has to do\n(go to Clark Gable)</string>

    <string name="problem_label">Problem?</string>
    <string name="problem_description">Leave those poor fools doing all the hard work. Why don’t I just sit down and start reading new hero daily magazine, about other fools doing the hard work. You would rather sit and enjoy pint of beer…</string>
    <string name="problem_quest_for_glory">End of story.\nDon’t like this?\n(go to Quest For Glory)</string>

    <string name="clark_gable_description">As you embark on quest of great… no… EPIC proportions, you must choose how to deal with upcoming menace…</string>
    <string name="clark_gable_send_castle">Seems I can do it… after all…\n(go to Sand Castle)</string>
    <string name="clark_gable_hero_party">I can\'t do it after all… I need to search for quest companions\n(go to Hero Party)</string>
    <string name="clark_gable_loshmi_the_gray">Who cares… I am Tier 1 hero anyway..\n(go to Loshmi The Gray)</string>
    <string name="clark_gable_label">Clark Gable</string>

    <string name="sand_castle_description">You made it… CASE is solved, and you can bask in your glory.\n\nFrom town to town, your name will be singed, young virgins will repeat your name in their dreams, and jealous husbands will curse you because after tale of your deeds they will never be top male in their wife’s hearts.</string>
    <string name="sand_castle_label">Sand Castle</string>

    <string name="hero_party_description">As you enter smoky old dusky tavern, you can see several hard looking fellas, who go about their own business… Seems none of them is noticing you coming in…</string>
    <string name="hero_party_tier2">I will ask party of semi-veterans, they look capable of doing the muscle work for me.\n(go to Tier 2)</string>
    <string name="hero_party_tier3">I chose to ask veteran party… Better to have more than less.\n(go to page Tier 3)</string>
    <string name="hero_party_dacha_turkish_terror">I will ask Dakinsa… old friend from thousands battles to help me… more XP for both of us…\n(go to Dacha theTurkish terror)</string>
    <string name="hero_party_label">Hero Party</string>


    <string name="loshmi_the_gray_label">LoshMi The Gray</string>
    <string name="loshmi_the_gray_description">As you expose your problem to LoshMi, you can see hint of his smile, as would you look upon child who would try to fight his way with wooden sword against old Oak tree…</string>
    <string name="loshmi_the_gray_soothsayer">Young one, if you want to hear my advice, go far to the north, where mountains touch the sky, where clouds dance among eyes of ones who watch it. There will you find Pedja the oracle\n(go to page Soothsayer)</string>
    <string name="loshmi_the_gray_bridge_of_doom">I help you will… if you do thou quest for me\n(go to Bridge of doom)</string>
</resources>
